EDWIN AU

WEB DEVELOPER | GRAPHIC DESIGNER

https://edwinau.github.io/edwin-landing



https://www.linkedin.com/in/eaudesign



416-880-3791



edwinau@rogers.com

PROFILE As a creative web developer with experience in graphic design and product design, I'm passionate about creating modern and intuitive applications that puts user experience at the forefront. I abilities in providing solutions and pin-pointing shifts at the ever changing user needs. Please feel free to reach out and see how I can benefit your team.

EDUCATION



Web Development Program

Mar 2017 - Jun 2017

> Full Stack Web Immersive

> JavaScript, Ruby, Rails, HTML5, CSS3, ¡Query, AJAX, SQL, SASS, HAML, Sketch



B.A.A. - Fashion Design Degree

Sep 1998 - April 2002

> Product design, graphic design, marketing, trend analysis.

> Strong presentation & communication skills. R&D experience.

Central Saint Martins (UK)

Experimentation Design Course Jan 2001 - Aug 2001

> Selected by Ryerson University to partake in this foreign exchange program.

> Thesis: Triple bottom line & green design.

WORK EXPERIENCE

▲ RendezYou

Web Developer | Graphic Designer @ Mar 2017 - Present https://rendezyou.herokuapp.com

- > Responsive design across all browser platforms; Full-stack CRUD development.
- > Built on HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Adobe CS6, Ruby, Rails, jQuery, SQL.

Thinkway Toys

Design Manager | Packaging Designer @ Mar 2016 - Mar 2017 www.thinkwaytoys.com

- > Design Manager in licensed harlines products; Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign:
 - Lucas Films | Star Wars Rogue One
 - Disney/Pixar | Cars 3
 - Universal Studios | Despicable Me 3

■ Disney Consumer Products

Product Developer, Brand Designer ② Nov 2013 - Mar 2016 www.dcpi.disney.com

- > Provided creative leadership in the design and development of Disney Branded Consumer Products sold across Canada.
- > One of five designers working out of Disney Canada's head office. Guiding 50+ licensees on product design ranging from apparel and home accessories, to toys and arts & crafts. These products were widely sold at Walmart Canada, Target Canada, Dollarama, Canadian Tire and Toys R' Us.
- > Work days range from approving product designs online, to traveling and meeting with vendors communicating Disney design goals and initiatives.
- > Researching market analysis, trend forecasting (15%); Managing/coordinating (35%); Implementing (40%); Reporting (10%).

Dolce & Gabbana (Milan, Italy)

Associate, Graphic Designer ② Sep 2012 - Sep 2013

- > Having accumulated 10 years of product development experience in Toronto -I decided to take my skills as a Technical Designer, Fashion Designer, and Product Developer abroad, ending up with the opportunity to work at Dolce & Gabbana's head quarters in Italy Milan for a year, helping their design and sales team with preparation and sales of their Fall 2013 and Spring 2014 collections.
- > Created Fall 2013 sales deck and Spring 2014 training material.

SKILLS





















Sketch



















